

Wahab Anjum

Full stack web app developer

Hard Skills

Front-end

Angular Framework

Typescript

Javascript

Ngrx *

Jasmine

Rxis

CSS

SASS *

Bootstrap

Html

VCS / Others

Git

GitHub

Scrum

Back-end

.NET Core / Asp.NET

Firebase

MVC LINO

MSSOL

Cloud

Azure Firebase smarterasp.net Netlify

IIS

As an experienced Full-Stack Developer, I specialize in Angular, Typescript, .NET, C#, and SQL. My dedication to delivering high-quality results and strong work ethic have earned me a reputation as a reliable and dedicated team member. I am committed to staying focused and productive throughout the day and have extensive experience working with Agile principles.

portfolio: pikuman.dev

Professional Experience

Full stack Developer

March 2022 - Present

For Unblur

Collaborated on migrating a complex software for emergency services from AngularJS to Angular 13.

Implemented SSO system including server setup.

Develop new features ensuring scalability and best practices.

Mostly using Angular, .NET, MySgl, Azure...

Full stack Developer - Freelance July 2020 - February 2022

For BB for Investors

Portfolio for Real Estate investors / Sept 21

Multi-language "Serverless" site with total autonomy for the client to add, edit or delete their projects (dynamically categorized in separate tabs) and news, upload photos, create users, personalized quotations & dashboards.

Angular, Firebase authentication, storage and Firestore cloud...

For: MB Tech

Financial Reporting & Business analytical dashboard app / Jan 21 -Mar 21

Angular, ASP.NET, SAP Crystal Reports, IIS hosting...

ERP / Jul 20 - Dec 20

An ERP which integrates Finance, Purchase, Sales & Production departments and provide 50+ reports for full business control. Angular, .NET Core, ASP.NET, SAP Crystal Reports, IIS hosting...

Detailed summary in Portfolio (link at the bottom)

Barceló Hotels Group

May 2006 - Present

Several departments

Managing individual bookings and quotations Client attention through email, phone and in person

IDEs / Libraries

VS Code Visual Studio MSSQL Management Studio Angular Material Ngx Charts

(*) Theoretical knowledge

Soft Skills

Organized & Self-demanding

Problem solving

Experienced teamworker

Analytical mindset

Hard-worker

Languages

Spanish: Professional Proficiency

English: Advanced

Catalan: Intermediate

Urdu/Hindi: Native

Punjabi: Native

Contact



Barcelona - Spain



(+34) 600 731 531



wahab_anjum[at]hotmail. com

New staff training

Event Organizing

Providing services in several F&B departments

Education

Intermediate in Computer Science September 1999 - March 2001

Govt Murray Collage - Sialkot, Pakistan

All the optional subjects were related to finance & statistics Co-founded a tech company "MB-TECH". Participated in multiple projects as a member

Current focus

Scrum from Cibernarium - Barcelona Activa Enhancing my knowledge of Rxis operators and Ngrx Looking forward to learn React Native

Interests

Committee member of Barcelona ultimate frisbee club. Playing and training students.

Committee member and active participant of popular culture's drums band

Playing badminton and Padel

Other interests: hiking, skiing, arcade games, running and cycling

Links

Portfolio:

pikuman.dev

Linkedin:

https://linkedin.com/in/wahab-anjum-47497675

Latest project analysis:

Proposal: pikuman.dev/argonia

Latest Project:

- · BB for Investors, Dummy-url: https://bbinvestors.netlify.app
- Proposal: pikuman.dev/propuestaBB
- · Github: https://github.com/pikuman83/bbInvestors